prepbootstrap.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy | PrepBootstrap

#### Information Collected

Our Site collects information regarding domain names, IP address (static or dynamic IP-address that sometimes point to a particular identifiable computer or device), type of browser, operating system, time of access and referring/exit web site addresses. This information is used by PrepBootstrap. for operational purposes, to maintain service quality and to track site trends and statistics. Most of the time, this information does not personally identify you. 

We also collect any personal information that you choose to provide when you use this Site. This may include, but is not limited to the events when you: create an account, order and/or download products, contact our sales department, post content in our forums or interact with other areas of our support center. This information of personal nature may include, your name, e-mail address, and any other information selected by you to share. We may collect any additional personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide through such posting, contact or interaction, in cases when you post content in the forums, interact with other areas of our support center, or contact our sales department or support teams, In case you sign up for any PrepBootstrap. newsletter, webinar, survey, other communication or you just want to make general contact with us, we will collect information of your contact to fulfill your request. In case you wan to unsubscribe, follow the unsubscribe link that appears at the end of each communication or, you may unsubscribe via your account preferences. 

#### Use, Sharing or Disclosing of Personal Information

Please note that we do not sell or rent your personal information to any third party. The main purpose we use your personal for is to communicate with you in the most efficient manner. We may share, disclose, or provide your personal information with or to a third party: (i) in cases when we attempt to collect a payment or debt, (ii) when we are required to combat fraud or to protect our interests, (iii) in order to enforce the Terms of Use of this Site or other PrepBootstrap. Sites, (iv) in cases when we are required to do so by law or in order to respond to legal process or lawful requests, including from law enforcement or government agencies, (v) within and among our affiliates and subsidiaries, or (vi) as part of a merger or sale of a business. We may use or share your personal information for the purpose of delivering correspondence, communications, or services, such as newsletters, events, training or software that you request or purchase, as well as to make a notification to you about the status of your order. Any information you have provided may be used by us for the purpose of providing customer support to you. Note that, these third parties are authorized to use your personal information ONLY for the sole purpose of providing these services to us. 

#### Use of Cookies

Cookies are used by us occasionally. In their nature Cookies are small text files that can be used by a web site to identify/recognize a repeat visitor to the web site. Cookies may be used by us for variable reasons, including: 

  * To facilitate the navigation of our website
  * To help the sign up and login process for our services
  * To make your experience personalized
  * For analysis of page frequency visitation
  * In order to provide social sharing widgets and videos features of the website
  * To be able to measure effectiveness of advertising and promotions

In case you do not wish PrepBootstrap. to deploy cookies in your browser, you can opt out by changing your browser settings to reject cookies or to notify you when a web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, our Site can still be used by you but your ability to use some of the products and/or services at this site may be affected and full site functionality is not guaranteed. 

#### Information Security

We make sure that appropriate security measures are taken to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, use or disclosure. Among these measures are a variety of security technologies and procedures like data collection internal reviews, practices regarding storage and processing and also security measures and appropriate encryption and physical security measures. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) certificates to encrypt the transmission of data on the PrepBootstrap. payment and login pages. Please note that no transmission via the internet can be fully secure, therefore, on your side you are also responsible for taking the necessary measures for protection of your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, including protection of your password. Apart from the indications under “Use, Sharing or Disclosing of Personal Information”, access to your personal information is restricted ONLY to PrepBootstrap. employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information so that they can process it and provide personalized customer support to you. Note that these individuals are bound by strict confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination in case they fail to comply with these complications. 

#### Credit Card Processing

A third-party service provider is used by us to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use your personal information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf. 

#### Revision of Personal Data

PrepBootstrap retains minimum Personal Data that is reasonable and needed in the management and maintenance of a product supplier to customer relationship. PrepBootstrap customers may review and update their profile and subscription information on the PrepBootstrap website customer portal. 

If you have issues revising your Personal Data, send mail to admin@prepbootstrap.com and state your need and contact information for help. 

#### Retention and Deletion of Personal Data

PrepBootstrap will retain your Personal Data for as long as your account is active; as needed to provide you products or services; as stated in the Terms of Use agreement; as needed for the purposes outlined in this policy or at the time of collection; as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, honor UNSUBSCRIBE requests, meet financial audit requirements and enforce our agreements; or to the extent that is permitted by law. 

If requested, PrepBootstrap will delete your Personal Data in a manner that ensures your identify cannot be reconstructed or read. A deletion request may not result in the entire deletion of your data. Purchase information will be maintained for legal and financial audit purposes. Forums submissions will be retained as per the Terms of Use Agreement and your name will be removed. If you wish to remove your Personal Data, send mail to [admin@prepbootstrap.com](mailto:admin@prepbootstrap.com) with "Subject: Remove My Personal Data" and explicitly state your need and contact information. 

#### Personal Data Transfer, Processing and Storage

The Personal Data that we store is not highly sensitive and is needed in order to conduct normal and expected business practices. Specifically, Personal Data, as described in this policy, is stored on US-based data servers or in Cloud Storage Services managed by US and International companies. We and all third party companies with which we engage with have committed to complying with the 2018 EU GDPR privacy regulation for EU residents. Based on the Lawful basis definition, as defined by the EU GDPR regulation, PrepBootstrap's use and storage of minimal Customer Personal Data, the Legitimate Interests basis is the appropriate legal basis of data storage and use. It is a reasonable and expected use of customer and prospective customer data.
